Hello friends, you all are very welcome to our
news channel Share Market Ki Seedhi Baat
SMSB.
Friends, in this video we will talk to you about
ICI CI Lombard Company.
Friends, the company has
released its quarter to quarter results 2026.
Friends, if we look at the total profit of the company,
it has increased by more than 18%
and this increase has been
recorded on a year by year basis.
If we talk about the total income of the company, then it has
registered an increase of more than 12%.
Friends, the company has
also announced a dividend of ₹6.50 and its
record date has been fixed as October 23, 2025.  This
means that
whoever holds the company's shares till this date will have to pay
dividend.  Thanks friends.
See you in the next video.  Video Likes